lipstickalley.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Notice - Lipstick Alley

### » Privacy Notice

**Lipstick Alley Privacy Notice**

This Lipstick Alley Privacy Notice describes how we treat personal information when you use Lipstick Alley's message board.

**Collection of data**

Personal information is only collected when you register for an account. The only information collected is your email address and IP address. While you browse the site certain non-personal information is collected in the site’s access log, such as the type of browser and operating system you use, your IP address, the date, time and the forums you visited, and if you followed a link to this site from another website.. This information does not identify you personally. The access logs are processed daily by a log analyzer and then deleted.

The only time your IP address is recorded is when you register for an account. It is not recorded when you post on the forum.

We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties.

We will not disclose your personal information to a third party without first receiving a valid civil subpoena. In the event that we receive a valid subpoena, we will promptly notify the account holder whose information is sought.

**Cookies**

We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a website server and stored on your computer’s hard drive that help us to recognize you if you visit this site again. Cookies are not designed to get data from your hard drive or your email. To protect your privacy, we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice..
